# 哈喽 大家好
Hey guys
# 最近我买的这个三眼灶已经到了
I bought a three-ring stove and it’s here now
# 这个是我们厨房里面非常专业的一个灶
It’s a very professional stove in our kitchen
# 为什么叫做三眼灶呢
Why is it called "three-ring"?
# 它有三个开关
It has three valves
# 但是它是在一个炉膛里面有三圈火
In one burner, it has three rings of flames
# 这里一圈两圈三圈
Here, one, two, three rings
# 分别用三个不同的开关来控制
Controlled by three separate valves
# 大家猜一下这个灶是用来做什么的
Can you guess what this stove is for?
# 然后这是一个节能灶
It’s an energy efficient stove
# 节能灶的话要配上一个节能的桶
This energy efficient stove needs to have an energy efficient pot
# 比如说这一个
Like this one
# 这个是直径50公分的一个桶
This pot has a diameter of 50 centimeters
# 这个是50升的
It has a volume of 50 liters
# 是专门用来煮汤啊做卤水啊之类的
It’s used for cooking broth and master stock
# 然后大家可以看一下这个下面
And let’s look down here
# 跟我们普通家庭里面有一些不一样
It’s different from the ones we have back home
# 它这里有很多圈有很多小格
It has lots of rings and grating
# 就跟迷宫一样
Like a maze
# 也不知道是谁发明的
I don’t know who invented this
# 但是这个东西大概可以节能40%左右
But this pot can save energy by about 40 percent
# 现在我来把它装上去试一下
Let’s assemble it and have a try
# 现在先把这个管子上上去
Let’s hook this tube on
# 我们这个管子跟一般的不一样
The tube is also different from the regular ones
# 这个中间是有钢丝的
It has steel wires built in
# 这个也是非常耐用
Making it extra durable
# 非常专业的
Really professional
# 好 这个上好了
Alright, this is good
# 然后这个我们也用高压阀
We are also using high-pressure regulators for the stove
# 如果用低压阀的话可能气上面有一点问题 火力有问题
The regular-pressure regulators will have problems on gas and burner capacity
# 这个水的话
For the water here
# 你看我倒了一盆水进去
You can see I pour a pot of water in
# 可能只需要一分钟不到就可以烧开
And it will boil in less than a minute
# 好 我现在端开给你们看一下里面
Alright, let me move this and see the bottom
# 这个水已经开了
The water is already boiling here
# 看一下 已经开了
See, boiling
# 好了 现在给你们看一下这个下面
Alright, let’s see the bottom of the pot
# 到底是怎么样子的
What it looks like
# 我拿这一个给你们看
Let me grab one for you
# 看 这个就像那个
Look, it is like
# 把这个火力啊均匀的分配在这里
The heat can be evenly distributed here
# 就是说能够保证它每一片
Guarantees that each sheet
# 每一个地方都能够有火力
Can be evenly heated
# 都可以到这个地方
The heat can be evenly distributed
# 它就不像家里面那个平的平底锅
Unlike the flat pans we have back home
# 火一开如果火够散的话
If the burner is a little scattered
# 它就往一边偏 或者怎么样
The heat will lean towards a certain side
# 或者这里烧不到
Some parts won’t be heated
# 或者这里会烧得很烫
And some parts will get burnt
# 这个设计非常的不错
It’s a really good design
# 然后大家肯定对这个价格有点感兴趣
And you may be interested in the price
# 这一个的话是95升的
This one has a volume of 95 liters
# 然后是一个加厚的一个不锈钢
It’s the extra thick version made of stainless steel
# 这个就稍微贵那么一点点
So it’s a bit expensive
# 大概是400块钱
About 400 yuan
# 然后这里这个小的
The smaller one here
# 这刚刚烧开水这个是300多
The one we boiled water with is over 300 yuan
# 比这个要便宜二三十块钱
20-30 yuan cheaper than the big one
# 但是这个可以多装很多
But it can still hold a lot
# 然后放下来 大家可以看一下这个
Let’s put it down and have a look at this
# 这个三眼灶就是三个圈圈的这个灶
The three-ring stove is this stove with three rings of burners
# 是加厚的商业版本
It’s the thicker commercial version
# 就是很耐用非常耐用的一个低灶
It’s a very durable stove
# 这个大概是500块钱的样子
It costs about 500 yuan
# 所以我们买这些专业的东西
The reason we buy all these professional appliances
# 当然是要做更专业的事情
Is to do professional cooking of course
# 就是可能会分享一些
So later we are going to share some videos
# 就是你们平时看不到的东西
Those you can’t usually see
# 当然这些专业的东西可以把它量化成小的
Of course, these professional appliances can be scaled down
# 可以在家里面也可以做
So that we can use them back home
# 好啦 本期视频就到这里 拜拜
Alright, that’s it for this episode, bye